莫斯科
伙计  你就不想问我点什么吗
So, bud, did you want to ask me anything?
不  斯科特  我没啥想问的
No, Scott, I don't think I do.
好吧  难道你就不想问我
Hmm. So you don't want to ask me
那些钻石值多少钱吗
how much those diamonds are worth?
我还以为你想知道呢
'Cause I think you do.
你和医生谈过了吗
Did you talk to the doc?
压力太大了而已
Stress.
这几年总要背着我的搭档
It's years of carrying my partner.
我觉得我都瘦了呢
I thought I've lost weight.
确实如此  你真的瘦了
You have. You have lost weight.
这些人是不是走错地方了
You think those guys are lost?
应该不是
No.
要不下去和他们交个朋友
Should we go and make some new friends?
行  这个可以有
Yeah, I think we should.
精英小组怎么没来
What's with the "A" Team?
他们不认识你们
They don't know you, and they don't want
也不想招惹阿卡帝·乌尔诺夫
trouble from Arkady Ulyanov.
你想招惹他不成
Were you expecting some?
乌尔诺夫那份少不了他的
Ulyanov always gets his cut.
你们不说我们也不会自找麻烦
We won't tell if you don't.
东西带来了吧
Hmm. You got the stuff?
这可是莫斯科最好的可卡因
The best cocaine in Moscow, OK?
不错
Nice.
钱呢
The money.
你带钱了吗
Did you bring it?
没啊  伙计  好吧
No, dude. Oh.
我没带啊
I didn't bring it.
伙计  不是该你带钱的吗
You were supposed to bring it, dude.
伙计  我没带啊
Man, I didn't bring it.
靠  抱歉
Shit. Sorry.
不需要动枪的  没事的
Hey, you don't need to draw that. It's all right.
你们收支票或者信用卡了吗
Do you guys take a check or credit cards?
嘿  别激动  别激动
Hey, it's all right. No, no, no.
你们陷害我们
You set us up!
-你们陷害我们  -不要开枪
- You set us up! - Don't shoot!
不要 别开枪
No, don't shoot!
快上车
Get in the fucking car!
别开枪  别开枪
别开枪
这对缓解我的压力可没啥用啊
This really isn't helping my stress.
快开车  开车  别开枪
Go, go! No, no, don't shoot!
别开枪
Don't shoot!
我的二舅姥爷啊
Jesus Christ!
别开枪  别开枪
你说的什么呀  朝我们开枪吗
What are you saying, "Shoot at us"?
我觉得他们可听不进去  迈克尔
I don't think they're listening, Michael.
这次任务没让我们来送死啊
Dying is not part of this mission!
我们死不了的  斯科特
We are not gonna die, Scott.
靠
Shit!
别开枪  别开枪
Whoa, stop shooting! Stop shooting!
啥  你以为说英语就有用吗
What, you think saying it in English is gonna help?
什么
What?
伙计  你这车技真让他们气得够呛
Well, you always piss 'em off with your driving, dude.
你怎么开车和我一个德行了啊
You're starting to drive like me!
这车还要飙多久啊
How long are we gonna keep this up?
别开枪
Don't!
好吧  我觉得该停车了
All right, I think we should stop now.
-你要停车吗  -停车
- You want to stop? - Yeah.
抓稳了啊
All right, hold on.
下次我来开
Next time I'm driving.
我们  我们在找莫斯科大剧院
We're, uh, we're looking for the Bolshoi.
达米恩·博克     迈克尔·纽曼
长官  我们已经证实
Sir, we have confirmation of
斯科特和斯顿布奇已经被捕
Scott and Stonebridge's arrest.
莫斯科  20号分部
收到
Copy that.
他们连上了
They're in.
将北约和白宫接到五号线
I want NATO and Whitehall online in 5.
长官
Sir.
演坏人没有想象的好玩
This bad-guy shit's not as much fun as I thought it'd be.
48小时前  朱海瑞恐怖组织
48 hours ago, Al-Zuhari terrorists
袭击了布达佩斯的英国大使馆
attacked the British Embassy in Budapest
复制了一个北约的硬盘
and cloned a NATO hard drive.
并检测到其被访问时
An ID pulse from the clone was detected
发出的特殊脉冲信号
when someone attempted to access it.
这个硬盘是加密的
Well, the hard drive is totally secure.
该脉冲信号来自俄国的黑熊监狱
The pulse has been traced to Black Bear Prison, here in Russia.
欢迎来到黑熊监狱
是一所私营监狱
It's privately run.
由黑帮老大维克多·乌尔诺夫掌管
Mafia boss by the name of Arkady Ulyanov.
上至州长的所有官员都收受他的贿赂
Everyone from the Governor down is on his payroll.
把他们带走
高度可信的情报证实
A high-value source has confirmed
乌尔诺夫和朱海瑞是一伙的
Ulyanov is working with Al-Zuhari.
脱衣检查
什么意思
What does that mean?
美国人先来
"Americans first."
手张开
操你
Fuck you.
操  好吧
Fuck. All right, all right, all right.
满意了吧
There you go.
这是什么
你老妈的电话号码
That's your mother's number.
-达米恩  -干嘛
- Damien. - Huh?
还挺爽的
It's going well.
要想进入北约数据库
They'd have to pierce 3 firewalls
得破坏三道防火墙才行
before they could access the NATO hub.
他们不可能...
There is no way--
他们做不到  但是这个人可以
They couldn't, but this man can.
电脑黑客艾瑞克·安德森
Computer hacker Erik Andersson.
由于泄露其同盟的在伊朗的行动机密
Currently being extradited to the U.S.
他最近要被引渡到美国
for leaking intel on allied operations in Iran.
安德森之前被关押在低安全级别监狱里
Andersson was in a minimum-security prison
三天前被转送到黑熊监狱
until 3 days ago, when he was transferred to Black Bear.
靠  靠
Fuck! Oh!
姑娘的号码你倒是过目不忘
You never forget a girl's number.
这个怎么记不住了
What's with this one?
这个不一样
This one's different.
为什么
Why?
就是不一样
Kinda special.
小心别让那些人知道
Make sure you get behind those ears.
你们通知俄国了吗
Have you informed the Russians?
没有正式通知
Officially, no.
联邦安全局内半数人都受乌尔诺夫的控制
Ulyanov also has half the Federal Security Service in his pocket.
但在不受控制的人里  有我内线
But I have a man inside the other half of the FSB.
你说的没错
You were right.
第一道防火墙十五分钟前已被破坏
The first firewall was breached 15 minutes ago.
必须阻止安德森
This Andersson has to be stopped.
我的人现已进入黑熊监狱
My men are already inside Black Bear with orders
受命销毁硬盘  并弄出安德森
to destroy the drive and get Andersson out...
如果失败就杀人灭口
or kill him if they can't.
带上硬盘  跑路就好
Grab that hard drive and get out.
伙计  我觉得没问题
Sounds great to me, dude.
安德森在那里
There's Andersson.
话说我们到底来这里干啥的啊
What the fuck are we doing in here, anyway?
乌尔诺夫如果发现我们在他的监狱里
Ulyanov finds out we're in his prison,
我们必死无疑
we're dead men walking.
那么...
Well...
你想冒险生点事吗
You want to risk a little unwanted attention?
-行啊  -我们猜拳决定吧
- Yeah. - Let's do the thing.
为什么  赢的总是你
Why? You always win.
我知道  所以我喜欢猜拳  来吧
I know. That's why I like doing it. Come on.
一  二
1, 2...
你去吧
There you go.
我过去打断他们
I'm gonna snag their fun,
把警卫从黑客小子身边引过来
strike those guards over there from Hacker Boy.
-你抓住他  -你去惹他们吗
- You grab him. - You want the evil elves?
没错
Yeah.
我觉得这挺好的
Yeah, I think it'll do me good.
你确定吗  阿迈
You sure, Mikey?
确定
Yeah.
那好吧
All right.
揍死他们
Go get 'em.
先生们  打扰一下
Gentlemen, excuse me.
能加我一个吗
Can't we all just get along?
嘿  你知道我们是谁吗
Hey, don't you know who the fuck we are?
我当然知道
I know exactly who you are.
那么大的纹身
Yeah, big tattoos,
微小的伤痕
tiny pricks.
我当然知道你们是谁
Yeah, I got a pretty good idea.
抓住他
安德森
Andersson.
你是谁
Who are you?
我们是来救你出去的
We're here to get you out.
我凭什么相信你
How do I know I can trust you?
你在伊朗泄露的那份情报中
Well, that intel that you leaked on ops in Iran?
保留了五名卧底的信息
You held back information
才让他们得以活下来
on 5 undercover operatives that would have died otherwise.
你觉得还有谁会知道这些呢
Now, who else would know that?
北约的硬盘在哪里
The NATO hard drive. Where is it?
我不能告诉你
I can't help you.
你成功破解硬盘后他们就会杀了你的
When you're done, they're gonna kill you.
他们抓了我的朋友
They have my friends.
我如果不就范  他们会死的
If I don't do what they want, they're all dead.
你以为你完成之后
You think that they're gonna let you
他们会让你和你朋友们离开吗
and your friends go when you're finished?
当你破解了最后一道防火墙
You break through that last firewall,
你和很多无辜的人们都会死
you and a whole lot of innocent people are gonna die.
事实就是如此
That's a fact.
那么你的朋友们在哪
So, your friends, where are they?
见鬼  我不知道
Hell, I don't know.
我只是在视频里见到他们
I only saw them on a video link.
好像是空的游泳池里
They were in some empty swimming pool.
其中一面墙上有一个军事标志
There was a military insignia on one of the walls.
你为我们拖延点时间
You buy us some time.
我们会找到你的朋友
We'll find your friends.
先照看好你的朋友吧
You might want to look after yours.
没错
Yeah.
迈克
Mike!
住手
Stop!
迈克  住手
Mike, stop!
你会打死他的
You're gonna kill him!
起来  过来  离他远点
Get off. Come here. Get off him.
深呼吸
Take a deep fuckin' breath.
把手机给我
Give me the phone.
过来  亲爱的
拉下去  把他转走
弱者在黑熊监狱无立足之地
In the Bear, there is no place for weakness.
清理广场
你想要我割了你的喉吗
Say, you want me to slit your throat?
滚开
Fuck off.
他们有人质
They got hostages.
可能得花更长时间
It's gonna take longer than we thought.
没错
Yeah.
你觉得我们的身份能瞒得住吗
You think our cover's gonna hold?
如果你总是干这些事
If you keep pulling shit like that,
难说
probably not.
谢谢  医生
Thank you, Doctor.
你那设备进展如何
How are things going at your facility?
应该差不多快完成了吧
Your work must be almost finished by now.
你的工作就是提供我所需的
Your job is to supply me with what I need.
其他的别多问
Nothing more.
等安德森干完活
When Andersson is done,
就要把他转移走
you will see he is transferred.
当然  医生
Of course...Doctor.
坐
Sit.
刚才你怎么了
What the fuck happened out there?
你还好吗
You OK?
我失控了
I've lost it.
心力交瘁
I'm burnt out.
你得坚持住  迈克
You got to hold it together, Mike.
-是啊  -我帮不了你
- Yeah. - I can't carry you.
在这里没办法
Not in here.
那些钻石值多少钱  斯科特
How much are the diamonds worth, Scott?
我要退出了
I'm done.
胆敢泄露我们在牢房里的所作所为
Oy, you talk about anything you see or hear in this cell,
你就死定了  明白吗
you're a dead man, is that clear?
那我先下手为强
Not before I cut your throat!
你来啊  爽吗
Oh, yeah? Yeah?
过来
Come here.
坐下
Sit down.
你这还有些什么
What else you got here, huh?
还有什么小惊喜
Any other little surprises?
-住手  -你别动
- No, leave it! - Wait. Come on. Stop.
不错啊
That's nice.
我不喜欢这颜色
It's not really my color.
还有些什么
What else we got?
果然有
Yep.
这真漂亮
That is really pretty.
是你的吗
Is it yours?
干你鸟事
Is none of your fucking business!
放松点
Easy.
你是怎么度过监狱漫漫长夜的
Whatever gets you through those long prison nights.
你不明白
You don't understand.
俄罗斯监狱里  都是弱肉强食
In Russian prison, they kill a man for less.
放松
Relax.
我们会为你保密的
Your secret's safe with us.
和平相处
It's all good.
那么
Then...
我也不会说出你们的事
I am deaf and blind.
莫斯科  国际银行
你想把所有资金转走
You wish to transfer all funds
然后关闭这些账户
and close each of these accounts?
有问题吗
There is a problem?
鉴于数额巨大  我们得做现金流量测试
Given the amounts, we are obliged to run some CFT checks.
到头来  说不定我是恐怖分子呢
After all, I could be a terrorist.
不  但是...
N-no, but, uh--
外表是有欺骗性的
Appearances can be deceptive.
你在广场的一番作为
The stunt you pulled in the yard.
除非你运气好或者你是穆斯林
That could get you transferred unless you're lucky,
否则他们会转移你的
or a Muslim.
为什么穆斯林不会
Why a Muslim?
不知道  有时候
Don't know, but sometimes,
他和日本人
this Muslim comes with Japanese
一起监督转移  但...
to supervise transfers, but...
他从不单独行动
he never takes his own.
知道他的名字吗
Does he have a name?
哈桑
Hussan.
李扎·哈桑
Reza Hussan.
转到哪儿去
Transferred where?
谁知道
Who knows?
你一旦被转移走
But once you're gone,
就没人能再见到你了
nobody hears from you again.
无一例外
Nobody.
破解硬盘中: 北约设备
安德森放慢了速度
Andersson is slowing it down,
但第二道防火墙已经破解一半了
but he's halfway through the second firewall.
看这个  是卡马里
Check this. Kamali.
我的人从俄联邦安全局查到的
My guys picked it up from the FSB.
他在做什么
What the hell's he doing?
中情局不知情
CIA have no idea.
凡·伯格已从柏林搭机过来
Van Berg's already on a flight from Berlin.
菲利普·洛克
Philip Locke.
是我
Yeah, it's me.
有点情况  我们需要更多时间
We got a problem. We need more time.
怎么了
Yeah?
安德森说他们绑架了他的朋友
He says they're holding his friends.
他是某个黑客公会的成员
He was part of some kind of hacker commune.
他要得知他们平安才会帮我们
He won't help us till he knows they're safe.
他从视频中看到他们被困在
He's seen them on video in some emptied-out pool,
某个有军事标志的空泳池里
military insignia.
还有  听说过李扎·哈桑这个人吗
Also, you heard of a guy named Reza Hussan?
他可能有参与到其中
He could have something to do with it,
与失踪犯人的事有关
something about disappearing prisoners.
他是朱海瑞得力队长之一
One of al-Zuhari's key lieutenants.
继续查下去
Find out what you can.
听着
Listen...
迈克尔的化验结果出来了
Michael's test results came through.
他沾染了一种神经毒素
He's been exposed to a neurotoxin, Scott.
他怎么样了
How is he?
有出现麻痹症状吗
Any paralysis?
可能有吧
Yeah, maybe.
斯科特  我建议你别告诉他  但你决定吧
My advice is you don't tell him, but it's your call, Scott.
他可能已处于晚期
He's probably in the last cycle.
如果是的话...
If he is...
病情会迅速恶化的
he will deteriorate rapidly.
可能就这一两天了
It could be a day, maybe two.
有没有解决的办法
Any thoughts on what we should do about that?
长官
Sir...
卡马里联系了凡·伯格
Kamali contacted Van Berg.
他要求见面
He wants to meet.
有一种解毒剂  斯科特
There is an antitoxin, Scott.
如果联邦安全局没法及时救我们出去呢
Yeah, and if your FSB guy doesn't get us out of here in time?
我们一旦救出人质
As soon as we have the hostages,
就会第一时间通知你们的
you'll be the first to know.
长官  这是李扎·哈桑
Sir? Reza Hussan.
一切顺利  伙计
All good, dude.
莫斯科  联邦安全局总部
祖科夫
这是什么
黑熊监狱的两个外国犯人
是乌尔诺夫要找的人吗
小声点  说英语
Quietly. Speak English.
他一人悬赏五十万美元
He is offering $500,000 each.
你是想独吞吗
You were going to keep them to yourself.
删除中
档案删除完毕
对半分
50-50.
阿迈  没睡吧
Mikey, you awake?
没睡
Yeah.
那些钻石
You know those dirty little stones?
价值差不多两百万
They're worth a little south of two mil.
妈的
Fuck.
-达米恩
- Damien?
想和我说说那个号码的事吗
You want to tell me what that phone number was all about?
我曾经是个混蛋
Once upon a time, I was an asshole.
曾经?
Once upon a time?
这个姑娘
There was this girl.
她怀孕了
I got her pregnant.
她和孩子跟着我都没什么好处的
What good was I gonna be for her or the kid, you know?
你离开她们了吗
Did you walk out on them?
是的
Yeah.
真是没脸见人
Not my proudest moment.
你原本有个孩子
It's a scary thought,
想都不敢想啊
the idea that you could have a kid.
阿迈
Mikey.
我有个好消息和一个坏消息
I got some good news and I got some bad news.
好消息是你没疯
Good news is you're not losing your mind.
坏消息呢
And what's the bad news?
你生病了
You're sick.
病入膏肓
Really fuckin' sick.
你沾染了某种神经毒素
You've been infected with some kind of neurotoxin.
你的手有点不听使唤对吧
You know how your hand's seizing up?
是的
Yeah.
不久你的腿也会这样
Pretty soon it's gonna go to your legs,
然后会扩散到你的肺里
and it's gonna get into your lungs.
一定是莱瑟比飞机场里那些炮弹的弹片
It was those shells at Leatherby's airfield.
还有多久
How long?
一天
A day.
或两天
Maybe two.
挺好的
Well, that's great.
我没疯
I'm not crazy.
我只是死定了
I'm just fucked.
洛克
Locke.
朱海瑞命令我注销他所有的账户
Al-Zuhari ordered me to close all of his accounts.
这男的跟着我
This man came with me,
我确定他会在搞定后杀了我
and I'm certain he had orders to kill me once it was done.
-为什么  -中情局
- Why? - CIA--
我问的是他
I asked him.
朱海瑞的手下怀疑有叛徒
Al-Zuhari's people suspect a traitor.
怎么  你觉得我应该
Oh, what? You think I should have
让他先杀了我吗
let him put a bullet through me first.
我他妈说的是实话
Yes, I'm fucking sure!
他们会杀了我的
They will kill me.
我有一个孩子
I have a child--
我曾有两个
I had two!
现在只有一个了
I now have one.
李奥  这不正是我们铤而走险的原因吗
Isn't that why we do this, Leo?
你必须要给我时间
You need to give me time.
上车
Get in the car.
-快点  上车  -快走
- Come on, get in! - Go, go, go!
有什么新情况
What did I miss?
安德森正在攻击最后一道防火墙
Andersson's through to the last firewall,
但进度变慢了
but the process has slowed.
与此同时  我们正在监控
In the meantime, we've been monitoring
区域内所有市军用游泳馆的动静
all movements of military municipal swimming pools in the area.
这个看起来有可能
This looks promising.
告诉我他的身份
Get me an ID.
搜索结果显示可能为李扎·哈桑
OK, we have a possible match for Reza Hassan.
这个荒废的体育设施位于郊区
It's a run-down sports facility on the outskirts of the city.
这消息够好的了
That's good enough for me.
整装出发
Kit up.
确保人质安全  然后就能拿下安德森
Secure the hostages, then we can get to Andersson.
遵命
Sir.
黑熊的监狱长正在转移囚犯
So, the Governor of Black Bear's moving prisoners,
已经证明朱海瑞与此事有关
and we have a link to Al-Zuhari.
眼下发生的事情
And it's happening now,
可能跟他接下来的计划有关
it might have something to do with what he's planning.
阿卡帝·乌尔诺夫控制了整个监狱
Arkady Ulyanov owns the prison.
我想让你们俩见面  弄清他都知道些什么
I want you two to meet. Find out what he knows.
等等
Just a second.
你知不知道
You realize,
想要杀我的很可能正是朱海瑞
in all likelihood, it was Al-Zuhari who just tried to kill me.
他的行动情报会保密的对吧
He operates on a need-to-know basis, right?
难道你想让乌尔诺夫发现
What, do you want Ulyanov to know
最高层里竟有一个叛徒吗
he has a traitor at the highest level of his operation?
李奥  你是唯一能胜任的人
You're the only man who can do this, Leo.
是吗
Yeah.
多谢你了
Thanks.
你觉得那枚炸弹是为你和凡·伯格准备的
You think that bomb was meant for you as well as Van Berg,
你在想...
and you're thinking--
道尔顿或许说对了一些事  没错
That Dalton might have got a few things right, yeah.
他最好站在我们这边
He better be on our side
因为我们需要动员所有朋友的力量
'cause we need all the friends we can get.
普希金  你外面有家人吗
So, Pushkin, you have family on the outside?
我老婆
My wife.
我女儿
My daughter.
但我再也见不到他们了
But I will never see them again.
你想出去吗
You want to get out?
当然
Of course.
想极了
Very badly.
你帮我们抓安德森  我们就把你弄出去
You get us to Andersson, we'll get you outta here.
普希金  你真的很想再见到家人对吧
You do want to see your family again, don't you, Pushkin?
我们给了这你机会
We're giving you that chance,
虽然有可能是自寻死路
even if it's just once, from across the street.
你们需要什么
What do you need?
分散注意
A distraction.
你想要一场骚乱啊
Oh...you would need a riot.
硬盘解密中  北约装置
你太慢了
You are too slow.
这并不容易  我得找到另一个密码
This isn't easy. I have to find another password.
你的同伙还等着呢
Your colleagues are waiting.
听着  朋友
Listen, my friend.
如果你敢耍什么花招
If you put me in a place where I have to explain failure,
我会让他们死无葬生之地的
you will look upon their quick and brutal deaths with envy.
安德森被单独关押在西侧
Andersson is kept in isolation wing.
只能通过B区进入
It can only be accessed through "B" Wing,
那儿终日严防
and guarded at all times.
钥匙呢
Keys?
只有门口的看守才有
Only guards at gate have them.
你怎么知道这些事的
How do you know all this shit?
我刚被关进来时
When I first sent here,
在隔离区待了很长一段时间
I spend much time in isolation.
所以解决了看守后  就能进去
So we take out the guards, we're in.
不  那里还有沃瑞的人
No. The Vory have free run of "B" Wing.
一群娘们
Fuckin' pussies.
"老狼"可不是
Hmm. Well, not The Wolf.
他是前特种部队
Ex-special forces.
俄罗斯特种部队
Spetsnaz.
然后呢
And then?
还有另一把钥匙  以及四个娘们
Another key and 4 more pussies.
为什么停车
你在做什么  祖科夫
我们的交易有点小变化
好吧
你拿百分之七十五
不耽误你退休
要退休的不是我
是你
混蛋
已定位泳池
待命
他们定位了人质  已经上路了
They've traced the hostages. They're on their way now.
很好
Good.
你好
Hello?
阿姆捷特
Amjad?
太慢了  太慢了
Too slow. Too slow! Too slow!
有一个技术故障
It's a technical fault.
代理驱动没有反应
The proxy drive doesn't answer--
不  安德森先生
No, Mr. Andersson.
有人让你故意拖延的吧
Somebody has told you to delay.
没有
No.
硬盘解密中  北约装置
不然你明知下场如何
Why else would you delay the program
怎么还敢耽误进度呢
when you know the consequences?
你觉得会有人来救你吗
You think somebody will save you?
不
No.
这是唯一的解释了
That is the only explanation.
不  我发誓
No. I swear.
打电话给哈桑
让他上线
亲爱的  看仔细点
视频连接中
是的
Yes.
是的  所有事都...
Yes, everything's...
李扎·哈桑
Reza Hassan.
让他们靠墙站好
快点
等等  你们在干什么  干什么
Wait. What are you doing? What are you doing?
站在相机前
谁联系你的
Who contacted you?
你的其中一位朋友会死
One of your friends will die.
谁联系你了
Who contacted you?!
别这么做
Don't do this.
杀了那男孩
Kill the boy.
不  不
No! No!
不不  求你了
No! No! Please!
不要  求你了
No! Please!
求你了  不要啊  求你了
Please! No! Please!
不要  不要  求求你们
No! No! Please!
-我们该行动了  -住手
- We have to move now. - Stand down.
如果我们在摄像机还开着时行动
If we move when the camera's on,
就会暴露斯科特和斯顿布奇
we compromise Scott and Stonebridge.
-那是个孩子  -别动
- He's a kid. - Hold.
不  不
No! No!
求求你们  换我吧  求求你们
Please, take me! No, please!
-安娜  我对不起你  -闭嘴
- I'm sorry, Anna! - Shut up!
真感人啊
How touching.
如果她真想那么做  换她来
If that is what she wants, let her!
没消息
Nothin'.
是谁联系你
Who contacted you?
我是故意的
I did it.
是我自己的决定
I decided to do it.
没人让我拖延时间
Nobody asked me to delay.
这东西会害死人的
They're going to kill people.
我不想同流合污
I can't be a part of that.
那么...
So...
我们这就将你拉下水
you will be a party to this.
杀了她
Kill her.
不要啊
No!
中断连接
待在这里
看着他们
快点把活干完  不然我们会杀光所有人
Just finish the job or we will kill the rest.
摄像关闭了  行动
Camera's off. Go.
我去追哈桑
I'm on Hassan.
人质已获救  准备行动
Hostages acquired, good to go.
明白
Roger that.
行动
操
Oh, fuck!
行动
该行动了  阿迈  你还好吗
We're on, Mikey. Are you gonna be all right?
还好
Yeah.
行动吧  普希金
Come on, Pushkin.
赶紧的
Come on.
这些囚犯将被移交给联安局
事关国家安全
还不快把门打开  蠢货
你搞什么鬼...
脸上那是什么
或许你该试试
他们会杀了他的
They're gonna kill him.
不  他会没事的
Nah, he'll be all right.
普希金
Pushkin!
跪下  贱人
普希金
Pushkin!
是的我穿上了裙子
我也化了妆
我高兴这样  你们有什么意见
但是
你们却甘心被这些混蛋关起来
你们保持沉默  无动于衷
看着你们的同志被一个个带走
接着
他们就消失了
他们被转移去哪儿了
他们都被谋害了
下面是我想对伊林说的话
去你妈逼
砸了这地方
毁了它
去死吧伊林
普希金  到这来  进去
Come here! Pushkin, come here! Get in, get in!
我们走  我们走
Let's go, let's go.
阿迈
Mikey!
普希金  穿上他的衣服把脸弄干净了
Pushkin, put his clothes on and clean your face.
奥斯卡影帝非你莫属了  干得漂亮  伙计
That was an Oscar-worthy performance there. Well done, mate.
化妆舞会开始了
Now we're gonna play dress-ups.
快点  快点
Come on, come on.
他们突破了B区
用催泪弹
我猜那位就是"老狼"
I take it that's The Wolf.
就是他
That's him.
他拿铲子做什么
What the fuck's he doing with a shovel?
俄国特种兵喜欢用铲子
Spetsnaz love their shovels.
给
Here.
-总比手无寸铁的好  -开什么玩笑
- Is better than nothing. - Fucking kidding me?
你去找安德森  我来对付这家伙
You're gonna go get Andersson. I'll get this guy.
伙计  来这儿练练
Hey, pal, fight's that way.
你拿个铲子打算干什么
What are you gonna do with that shovel?
挖点土豆做家酿伏特加吗
Dig up some potatoes and make some homemade "Wodka"?
你们也想试试吗
You want some?! Huh?!
躲开
Back off!
迈克
Mike!
我们在这儿
We're in here.
什么
What?
是催泪瓦斯  戴上这个
It's tear gas. Put that on.
催泪瓦斯进来了
Tear gas coming.
把那个包在你脸上
Wrap that around your face.
好了吗  我们走
All right? Let's go.
用实弹
伊林吗
Ilyin?
我是联安局的
FSB.
我要这俩人
开什么玩笑
整个监狱都封锁了
你不是应该有个搭档吗
我在路上把他杀了
这个解释如何
知道我为谁卖命吗
带我去见他们  不然我把你也杀了
把门打开
这两个人要单独看押
B区
"B."
穿过这儿就是了
Is right through there.
太晚了
It's too late!
你们来的太晚了
You're too late!
安娜死的不明不白  你们这些该死的混蛋
Anna died for nothing, you fucking bastards!
-够了  -你们骗了我
- Enough! - You lied to me!
你们这些骗子  已经被破解了
You lied! It's decrypted!
-冷静点  -太晚了
- Calm down. - It's too late!
-闭嘴  -坐下  坐下
- Shut up! - Sit down! Sit down!
你冷静点
Now calm down.
你的其他朋友都自由了
The rest of your friends are free.
我们要把你带出去
We're gonna get you out of here.
伊林来了
Ilyin.
是伊林
-看着他  迈克  -好的
- On him, Mike? - Yeah.
待在这别动
Stay.
-哪边  -这边
- Which way? - This way.
阿迈  有五个武装守卫朝我们这来了
Mikey, I got 5 armed guards coming at us.
起作用了
That worked.
我们跟他们谈判如何
谈个屁
我是妮娜·皮拉戈娃少校
I am Major Nina Pirogova
来自俄罗斯情报安全部门
from Russian Intelligence Security.
我没带武器
I am unarmed,
我一个人过来了
and I'm coming in alone.
这叫没带武器  去你妈的
Unarmed, my ass.
进去
Walk.
有个人很想跟你聊聊
There is a man who is very keen to speak with you.
把电话给他
Give him the phone.
看住她了
Got her?
去你妈的  乌尔诺夫
Yeah, fuck you, Ulyanov.
看来你们已经见到皮拉戈娃少校了
So, I take it you've met Major Pirogova.
长官
Boss.
是的  她跟我们在一起
Yeah. She's with us.
你是洛克的内线
You're Locke's inside man?
我看起来像男人吗[对上文man的咬文嚼字]
I look like a man to you?
还我武器
My weapon.
是  硬盘已经毁掉了
Yeah, the hard drive's destroyed,
但我们来迟了
but we were too late.
不  他已经完成了破解
No, he already completed the decryption.
无论朱海瑞想要什么  他已经得手了
Well, whatever al-Zuhari wanted, he's gonna have it.
等等  你要干什么
One second, one second. What are you doing?
我的工作是带你们离开这里
My job is to get you out of here.
不包括他
I can't do it with him.
别让她这么做  你说过会带我出去的
Don't let her do this. You said you'd get me out.
他妈的
Shit!
一切都在掌控之中
这家伙归你们了
过来  过来
护送少校
我们有护卫队了
We have an escort.
把枪扔了跟我走
Lose the guns and move.
这家伙是谁
Who the fuck is this?
普希金
Pushkin.
要么他跟我们走  要么你自己走
He's with us or you're on your own.
菲利普  我们要出去了
Philip, we're moving out.
电话  你的电话  拿着电话
Take your phone, your phone. Take your phone.
一切都在掌控之中
走吧
Walk.
洛克从哪找来的女汉子
Where'd Locke find a guy like you?
闭上你的臭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
莫斯科  乌尔诺夫宅邸
进来
银行是怎么回事
What happened at the bank?
钱必须得转移走
Money had to be moved.
这些是最后的准备
These are the final preparations.
你为什么到这来  李奥
Why are you here, Leo, hmm?
来跟你谈谈朱海瑞的计划
To talk to you about al-Zuhari's plans.
接着说
Go on.
我们想问你要些东西
We need something from you.
还有吗
More?
是的
Well...
作为回报  我们可以给你梦寐以求的东西
in return, I can give you what you truly want more than anything.
枪收起来吧
一切正常
你怎么样
How you doing?
真是好极了
just brilliant.
今天来的两个外国人
他们杀了我的儿子
把他们带来见我
立即马上
立刻逮捕少校
站住
这他妈是怎么回事儿
What the fuck?
快走  他们盯上我们了
Move. They're on to us.
走这边
We go this way.
肯定还有另外的出路
There must be another way.
那是安德森
That's Andersson.
我保证过会带他出去的
I promised we'd get him out.
他没救了  阿迈
He's gone, Mikey.
我们得带你去医院
We got to get you to a hospital.
普希金
Pushkin.
那就是转移犯人用的车  是吧
That's the transfer vehicle, right?
他们会把他带去
They're taking him
同一个地方吧
to the same place they took the others?
无论朱海瑞的计划是什么
Whatever al-Zuhari's planning,
那肯定是其中的一部分  斯科特
that must be a part of it, Scott.
好的  我去
Fine. I'm gone.
谁都不许离开
Nobody is going anywhere.
该死的
Fuck!
带我们离开这儿
Get us out of here.
我们哪也不去  他病了
We're not moving. He's sick.
我在这等他回来
I'm waiting right here until he comes back.
我起码得活着带一个回去
I'm getting at least one of you back alive.
-你不会对我开枪的  宝贝  -是吗
- You're not gonna shoot me, sweetie. - Yeah?
试试看
Try me.
带路
Fucking move!
普希金  不要
Pushkin, don't do it.
普希金  操
Pushkin--fuck!
我们离开这儿
Let's get you out of here.
开枪
立刻向他们开枪
这条路通往这栋楼的一处废弃点
This lead to part of building they no longer use.
我们或许能离开这
It's possible we get out here.
锁住了
It's locked.
过来
Come here.
好枪法
Good shot.
站住
快点儿
Come on.
-走  走  -该死的
- Go, go. - Fuck.
-进去  -谢谢
- Get in. - Thank you.
-快走  -谢谢你
- Go on. Go. - Thank you!
待在原地
别动
我可不是针对你
Don't take this personally,
不过你的计划得再多些变通
but your plan could use a little more finesse.